Archives & Special Collections University of Nebraska–Lincoln Libraries
Carlton and Territa A. Lowenberg Collection on Emily Dickinson and Music
- Cassette Tape Recordings, 5
  - Cassettes ED 35-52 (Box 22)
    - Vehar, Persis, Three from Emily (Box-folder 49.)
      Noncommercial cassette tape. Elizabeth Holt Brown, soprano; Nancy Anderson, cello; Persis Vehar, piano. ASCAP. "How happy is the little stone"; "The martyrs even trod" ["Through the strait pass of suffering"]; "Ashore at last" ["On this wondrous sea"]
    - Wallach, Joelle, Of Honey and of Vinegar: a Cycle of Four Songs for Mezzo and Two Pianos Based on Four Poems by Emily Dickinson (Box-folder 50.)
      Noncommercial cassette tape. Isabelle Ganz, mezzo; David Levi and Christopher Vassiliades, piano. "Split the lark and you'll find the music"; "How soft the prison is"; "As imperceptibly as grief"; "The Bible is an antique volume"
    - Waters, James (Box-folder 51.)
      Noncommercial cassette tape. Side A. Songs of Life. Daune Mahy, soprano; Cleveland Chamber Orchestra; Edwin London, director. September 28, 1986. Janice Harsanyi, soprano; Fred Ormond, clarinet; Carolyn Bridger, piano. January 22, 1984. "I taste a liquor never brewed"; "God made a little gentian"; "Far from love the heavenly father"; "From all the jails the boys and girls"
      Side B. Goal. Mary Sue Hyatt, mezzo; KSU New Music Ensemble; Frank Wiley, conductor. February 1983. "I felt a funeral in my brain"; "Least bee that brew"; "Each life converges to some centre"; "I felt a cleaving in my mind"
    - Ziffrin, Marilyn J., Symphony for Voice & Orchestra: Epilogue Letters (Box-folder 52.)
      Noncommercial cassette tape. N.H. Music Festival. Tom Nee, Music Director, Neva Pilgrim, soprano. This is my letter to the world. [Includes excerpts from letters by other writers]